jeffreynewyork.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy

##### **Jeffrey Customer Privacy Policy**

We respect your privacy, and take great care to safeguard information in our possession. Your preferences for use of your information are our highest priority.

 Jeffrey and the Nordstrom family of companies (Nordstrom, Nordstrom Rack, Nordstrom.com, Nordstrom fsb, Nordstrom Canada, Jeffrey, HauteLook and Trunk Club, Inc.) takes seriously the protection and proper use of your personal information, including social security numbers. In this policy, we may use "we," "our," "us" and "Nordstrom" to refer to the Nordstrom family of companies.

Jeffrey does not share customer information (including e-mail addresses) outside the Nordstrom family of companies unless it is necessary to provide you with products or services available from Jeffrey. We may also disclose information when you tell us to do so, to identify or contact you, to protect your rights or the rights of Jeffrey or as required or permitted by law.

Even within the Nordstrom family of companies, we restrict access to your information to those individuals who need it to provide you with products or services available from Nordstrom. Any third-party companies we use to provide you with products or services are required to keep your information secure and confidential.

##### **Jeffrey Privacy Policy Overview**

Welcome to Jeffrey. As a customer of Jeffrey and the Nordstrom family of companies, your trust is our most important asset. We take the protection and proper use of your personal information seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information in our possession. In order to preserve your trust, we want you to understand what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of this information.

In this policy, "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), address (city, state, zip), e-mail address, telephone number, etc.

This Privacy Policy governs your experience in our US stores and on this website unless otherwise indicated.

##### **Categories of Information We Collect**

We collect personal information when communicating or interacting with you through Jeffreynewyork.com, our stores or the Nordstrom family of companies. Some examples include:

  * registering for a shopping account, Wish List or Product Review account on our website
  * when you request that merchandise be sent to you or others, make purchases or returns with us, place an order with us online, via phone, mail, e-mail or fax, or request an e-receipt
  * fulfilling orders you place and delivering packages
  * requesting a catalog or other content and communications from us or when offering recommendations to you
  * subscribing to Jeffreynewyork.com E-mail Updates (our e-mail newsletter) or other communications from us or managing your preferences with us
  * applying for an account with us
  * your Financial Account numbers when transacting with us
  * interacting with our websites or mobile sites, mobile applications and services
  * when you participate in any of our programs such as contests, sweepstakes, surveys, loyalty programs, wedding programs etc.
  * when you apply for employment which may include your social security number or social insurance number
  * working with our salespeople who assist you with your fashion needs and purchases
  * through communications with you, or through the Nordstrom family of companies
  * when you are recorded by in store cameras used for safety, security and operational purposes, such as to measure traffic patterns in our stores
  * contacting us with a comment, question or complaint

We may also collect personal information about you from other third parties, such as demographic firms, to make our future service and marketing efforts more efficient and personalized for you. We may combine all information we collect and we may disclose this information within the Nordstrom family of companies or our service providers. When you visit our websites we may also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or other device identifiers, browser information, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, location, date/time stamp and clickstream data.

##### **How We Use Your Information**

We use the personal information that we and our service providers collect to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products, services and experience. We may collect and use your information to provide you products and services, notify you of product recalls or safety issues, process and respond to your application for current or future career opportunities, process membership requests when you apply or otherwise administer your participation in our programs, to respond to your comments, questions or complaints, determine your satisfaction with our programs and service, to personalize your experiences, if you ask us to, send you marketing communications and other information you have chosen to receive regarding our products, services, marketing or special events. We also use your personal information for our everyday business purposes such as security, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection and prevention, reporting, making back-ups and legal compliance.

##### **How We Share Your Information**

To best serve you, we may share your personal information with other members of the Nordstrom family of companies and with service providers that provide support services to us or that help us market our products and services, administer our programs, operations, fulfill your requests, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and product reviews, or provide you with membership information. Service providers, third parties who perform services on our behalf, are contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in helping us to provide you with the products and services available from Jeffrey. We may also, in certain instances, disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, to advise you of a product recall, detect and protect you or us from fraud, manage information security or bring legal action to protect your rights or the rights of Jeffrey or others. We may also disclose your personal information when you ask us to 

##### **Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Similar Technologies**

Our website uses "cookie" and "web beacon" technology. We use cookies and web beacons to identify your device, provide website user authentication, conduct fraud prevention and management services, distinguish you from other visitors, record your IP address and understand your use of our site, and identify the name of the Web site from which you linked to Jeffrey. This information is used for fulfilling contracts with our business partners, and to help us serve you better by improving our website design, as well as our products, services, and promotions. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. Information obtained through cookies and web beacons may be shared with or obtained by service providers on our behalf. More information is available under [Third-Party Advertising Partners](http://shop.nordstrom.com/c/nordstrom-com-privacy-policy#thirdpartyad).

A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available. A web beacon is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image and is used in conjunction with a cookie.

When you visit our website, we may use both a session and a persistent cookie. This Jeffrey-placed cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track your usage of our website and in some cases, your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is only saved in this Jeffrey-placed cookie if you register with us. A web beacon allows us to capture certain additional types of information about a visitor's actions on a web site, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time, date, duration and number of page views, a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed, and details about any items that were purchased.

If you register with us, this Jeffrey-placed cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our website and provides you with access to your account information. If you save your information with or order from us, we may also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. If you have not saved your information with or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. You can disable cookies at any time by using your browser options; however, if you turn off cookies, we will not be able to track your order or enable you to make a purchase from our website. In addition, we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user to allow you access to your account information.

We may use Flash Cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) or other similar technologies. A Flash cookie is a small data file placed on a computer using Adobe Flash technology that may be built into your computer or downloaded by you to your computer. We use these technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience, facilitate processes, personalize and store your settings. Flash cookies may help our website visitors to, for example, set volume preference associated with a video experience, play games and perform surveys. They help us improve our sites by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to customers. We do not use Flash cookies for marketing or behavioral targeting purposes. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies and the cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. [Learn how](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html) to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies or other similar technologies, please be aware that you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable.

##### **Third-Party Advertising Partners**

We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements (banners or links) on our behalf across the Internet.

These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your interactions with our products and services. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, e-mail address or other personal information. The information is collected through the use of cookies and pixel tags (also known as action tags), which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites.

In addition to the information about your visits to our website, our service providers may also use the information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products and services available from Jeffrey.

In the future we may partner with other companies to provide interest-based advertising, both on and off Jeffreynewyork.com. If this occurs, Jeffrey provides you with an opportunity to opt out when these advertisements are served. You may manage your third-party advertising preferences by clicking [here](http://privacy.thebrighttag.com/nordstrom/privacy-options.html "Privacy Options").

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

##### **Facebook Custom Audience Ads from Jeffrey  **

We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through a tool offered by Facebook called the Custom Audience Tool. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your shopping experience with us. We do not share any of your personal information, including your shopping history, with Facebook. The tool lets Jeffrey convert your e-mail address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers Facebook generates from e-mail addresses of its users. You may opt-out of Facebook Custom Audience ads from Jeffrey by clicking [here](https://nordstrom-fb-ad-optout.venturaassociates.net/).

##### **Social Media Interactions**

Jeffrey invites you to socialize and share your fashion inspiration, finds and purchases with your friends using Social Media tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram. If you choose to use these tools, you may be sharing certain profile elements, including your comments. This sharing is subject to each social media program's privacy policies. We also use Facebook Social Plugins to allow Facebook to share information and friends' activities with its members while they are on our website. For example, Social Plugins allow Facebook to show you and your friends' "Likes" on our product pages if you are logged into Facebook while shopping at Jeffreynewyork.com. Jeffrey does not receive or control any of the content from Facebook Social Plugins. To remove a Facebook "Like" through Jeffrey, place your cursor in the "grayed out" Like button and click on the "X" that appears. This removes the "Like" from your Facebook Page, as well as from Jeffrey websites. You can also delete comments made while at Jeffreynewyork.com from your Facebook Page.

For more information about Facebook Social Plugins and other social media tools, [click here](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/).

We may allow you to sign in to yourJeffreynewwork.com account using Facebook Connect. If you choose to do this, we may collect information necessary to facilitate social interactions such as friend lists, birthday, check-ins, basic profile information and your profile picture but only if the privacy settings you and your friends set within Facebook allow it. We will use the information we collect to create and facilitate an interactive social experience and to bring you products, services and programs from Jeffrey from Jeffrey. Jeffrey will always comply both with its privacy policy as well as with Facebook Connect terms regarding use of Facebook profile information.

##### **Links to Other Websites and Services**

Websites provided by Jeffrey and the Nordstrom  family of companies may include links to other Internet sites, content, or videos (embedded or direct links) maintained by third parties ('Linked Sites'). Jeffrey provides Linked Sites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of Linked Sites does not imply endorsement by Jeffrey of the Linked Sites. You access Linked Sites at your own risk and by accessing them you leave Jeffrey's website. Linked Sites are not under the control of Jeffrey and Jeffrey is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including the privacy policies or tracking technologies they may use. We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy to determine how they will handle any personally identifying information they collect from you.

##### **Browser Do Not Track Signals**

Although our websites currently do not have a mechanism to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals, we do offer our customers choices to manage their preferences that are provided in the previous sections above. To learn more about browser tracking signals and Do Not Track please visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.org/>

##### **_Video Recording_**

We conduct video surveillance at our stores for security, fraud and loss prevention purposes and for incident reporting purposes. We use the images and information from such videos only as required for such purposes and for certain operational purposes, such as to measure traffic patterns in our stores.

##### **Your Information, Your Choice**

To update us with your preferences, you may contact us using one of the following methods:

  * Call 1-866-554-6591, or
  * E-mail [privacy@nordstrom.com](mailto:privacy@nordstrom.com), or
  * Send your request to Nordstrom Privacy, PO Box 21986, Seattle, WA 98111

Please note your preference as stated below:

"I prefer not to receive e-mail advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events." (You may also click the designated link at the bottom of allJeffreynewwork.com e-mail advertisements to be removed from future e-mail updates.)

"I prefer not to receive direct mail advertisements, such as periodic catalogs and mailings regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events." (Please note that direct mail requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective.)

"I prefer not to receive marketing phone calls such as special events, special appearances, or promotions or new product arrivals from my salesperson or the company."

To update your Wish List privacy settings, you may select "Private" (not searchable) to protect your Wish List information from being publicly searched on our site or you may select "Public" (searchable). To protect your privacy, we initially set your Wish List account to a "Private" setting.

##### **Your Access**

We respect your need to be able to access and update the personal information that you have provided to us. If you have registered online, you may access and update your personal information at any time by logging into your account. You may also request access and update your personal information by e-mail or writing to the Nordstrom Privacy Office at the contact information set out below (subject to certain exceptions and as prescribed by law). We may request certain personal information to verify the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records.

##### **California Privacy Rights**

California law entitles residents to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or with corporate affiliates (such as Nordstrom Bank, Jeffrey,  and Trunk Club) for those entities direct marketing purposes.  Jeffrey does not provide any personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you want to request a notice or have any questions about Jeffrey privacy practices, please contact us at [privacy@nordstrom.com](mailto:privacy@nordstrom.com).

##### **Children's Privacy**

Jeffrey will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. If you are under 13 years old please do not provide your information on our website.

If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to Jeffrey for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files.

##### **Security**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personal information transmitted to us using this website. To help guard your information, our website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only Jeffrey is able to decode your information. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

To be sure your connection is secure, look at the bottom status bar of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser) the SSL is active and your information is secure. Most browsers offer additional security alerts as well. If for some reason you are unable to connect to our secure server, please call us toll free at 1-888-282-6060.

We also ask customers to carefully review their accounts and immediately report any unexpected activity to Jeffrey and their issuing bank or credit card company. Additionally, we are asking all our customers to take measures to help protect personal information in their online accounts, including the following:

  * Install the latest security updates and anti-virus software on your computer or mobile devices to help prevent malware and viruses
  * Reset your e-mail account password
  * Use complex passwords (a minimum of 7 alpha/numeric cAsE sEnsitive characters)
  * Do not use the same password on more than one website
  * Do not share your password with others
  * Password protect your personal mobile device(s)
  * Sign out/log off website sessions so that your session is closed and cannot be accessed by another user on the same computer, especially when using a public computer or terminal
  * Visit these additional resources: 
    * <http://www.us-cert.gov/cas/tips/>
    * <http://www.microsoft.com/security/pc-security/protect-pc.aspx>
    * <http://www.clarkhoward.com/news/clark-howard/technology/clark-howards-virus-spyware-and-malware-protection/nFZJ/>

##### **Fraud Alerts: Protecting Your Personal Information**

You may come in contact with websites, e-mails or texts that try to lure you into providing personal information with an offer such as a Jeffrey or Nordstrom gift card. Jeffrey and Nordstrom do not sponsor these offers nor are we affiliated with the promotion originators. If you become aware of any potentially fraudulent activity on a website or in an e-mail or text, please forward the information to [onlinefraud@nordstrom.com](mailto:onlinefraud@nordstrom.com) or call us at 1-888-282-6060  so that we can follow up. We take these matters, and the protection of our customers' sensitive information, very seriously. [View](http://shop.nordstrom.com/c/fraud-alert) our Fraud Alerts page.

##### **Data Processing and Storage**

Jeffrey and its third party service providers may process or store your personal information outside of the United States or Canada and other countries. In accordance with the laws of those countries, in certain circumstances your personal information may be accessible by foreign law enforcement, regulatory bodies or other authorities. For more information of our use of foreign service providers please contact us as described below.

##### **Business Transitions**

As we continue to develop our business, we may undergo a business transition such as acquiring another company, merging with an existing company, or selling a portion of our assets. In such transitions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. In the unlikely event that Jeffrey, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired or enter a court proceeding, you acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that your personal information can continue to be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

##### **Policy Changes**

This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on our website.

##### **Additional Information**

If you're not comfortable shopping online (and would prefer to make your purchase via telephone), just give us a call at 1-888-282-6060. Our Customer Service Representatives will be happy to assist you. For your convenience, Jeffrey may link to unaffiliated third party websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to unaffiliated third party websites.

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at:

##### **Nordstrom Privacy**

PO Box 21986  
Seattle, WA 98111-3986  
1-866-554-6591  

The examples contained in this Privacy Policy are illustrations only, and are not intended to be exhaustive.

_11/24/2014_
